The hijacking was just the beginning.
Non-Stop is a action, thriller, mystery film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra.
Bill Marks is a Federal Air Marshall for whom
every day is the same until this one.
On this plane ride, he starts receiving text messages from someone
claiming to be on the flight and threatening to kill passengers.
In a race against the clock, he must identify and stop
the killer to save everyone on board.
Bill Marks, played by Liam Neeson.
Jen Summers, played by Julianne Moore.
Tom Bowen, played by Scoot McNairy.
Nancy, played by Michelle Dockery.
Zack White, played by Nate Parker.
Kyle Rice, played by Jason Butler Harner.
Non-Stop is a 2014  action thriller film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra,
co-produced by Joel Silver, and starring Liam Neeson and Julianne Moore.
It follows an alcoholic ex-NYPD officer turned Federal Air Marshal who must find the killer on an international flight from New York
to London after receiving texts saying someone on board will die every 20 minutes until financial demands are met.
The film marks the second collaboration between
Collet-Serra and Neeson after Unknown (2011).
An international co-production among France, the United States, the United Kingdom and Canada, it was the first and only film
from Silver Pictures to be distributed by Universal Pictures since the end of Silver's deal with Warner Bros.
Released in the United States on February 28, 2014, the film received generally mixed reviews
from critics but was a box office success, grossing $222 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of airplane, bomb, fight, hijacking, murder.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.